# montycodes@gmail.com (310) 961-6410

# Jordan Montgomery

Full Stack Web Developer

## About Me

My name is Jordan Montgomery. I'm a 24 year old Full-Stack developer from Los Angeles, CA. I am currently looking for opportunities in the Los Angeles Area.

I am always excited to learn new things and I am a strong believer that there is nothing that I can't do or learn given time and hard work. I am constantly pushing myself to learn new skills as well as optimizing my current skills and always becoming more efficient.

I have a passion for building projects from the ground up, and I am committed to creating code that simplifies everyday life with practicality and logic. I often find my mind racing with ideas on how to tackle the current problem I am facing. There is so much to learn from trying to solve problems, even if your ideas don't pan out in the way you expected them to.

## Skills

0

02 FrameWorks	04 Knowledge
Django	Responsive Web Design
React	JSON
Angular	Sass
Node.js	jQuery
	GitHub
	Adobe Photoshop
03 DataBases	Adobe Premiere
MySQL MongoDB SQLlite	
	Django React Angular Node.js <b>03 DataBases</b> MySQL

# Work Experience

Pick 'Em All Sports, LLC UI & Front-end Consultant September 2017 - Current

Disneyland Resort

Attractions Cast Member October 2016 - January 2017

### Sport Chalet

Sales Associate / Cashier Ski / Snowboard Repair Shop Head Technician (2015) Department Head of Winter / Watersports (2016) October 2013 - June 2016

## **Hobbies**





Snowboarding





# Recent Projects

#### **Huber Rebels**

huberrebels.com

## **Summary:**

This website was created for my neighbor and I to post articles and videos relating to various topics in the video game industry. This website uses HTML and CSS. I am currently working on making the site scalable so it will easily grow as out content increases.

#### What I learned:

This is a project where I am spending a lot of time working on and practicing making the website responsive. I am looking into redesigning some of it using flex-box to scale and position everything exactly how I want it to look.

**Jamming** - (working title) monty-jamming.herokuapp.com

#### **Summary:**

This Web application was one of the final projects I worked on while taking a course on React. The application accesses the Spotify api to connect with your personal account. Using the search function, you can find music by name, artist, or album and add it to a custom named playlist. Once your playlist is complete, clicking "save to Spotify" adds the playlist to your Spotify account instantly.

#### What I learned:

This project gave me good practice working with multiple components that share and receive information with each other. It was a fun challenge integrating the ability to connect with your personal Spotify account.

## Two Thumbs Up

twothumbsup.online

# **Summary:**

Two Thumbs Up is a Web application created using TMDB (the movie database) api along with Django. We created an application which would allow users to rate movies and TV shows, as well as add them to a watchlist. The user would be able to follow other users and see their reviews of movies they watched. SQLlite was used with Django to store all of our information.

# My Role:

This was a group project during our time at the Coding Dojo, and has since been updated and better optimized. I helped with the overall design of the website and was tasked with implementing the api for TMDB.

# Education



### Coding Dojo

Web Design (yellow belt), Python (black belt), iOS (black belt), MEAN 2017



El Camino College Undergraduate Studies 2012- 2015

# **Additional Contact**







montycodes.com

/in/jordanmonty

/montyjoe